https://www.baystate.edu/internet-privacy-policy/

Criminal Justice
Criminal Justice, Cloud Security Risk Management Concentration
Criminal Justice, Digital Forensics and Cyber Security Concentration
Criminal Justice, Domestic and International Security Concentration
Information Technology, Business Analytics Concentration
Information Technology, Cloud Security Risk Management Concentration
Information Technology, Web and Mobile Development Concentration
Management, Marketing/Digital Marketing Concentration
Nursing (RN-BSN)
Health Studies
Nursing (ADN)
Nursing (LPN-RN)
Physical Therapist Assistant
Certificates
Graduate Program Partnerships
Salve Regina University Partnership: Master of Science in Administration of Justice and Homeland Security
Bay State College Internet Privacy Policy
Bay State understands that your privacy is important. We want you to know what information may be collected through this site and how it may be used. Continued use of this resource constitutes your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use the site.
What Personal Information May Be Collected When you visit the Bay State College website, our web server automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your browser, including your computer operating system, web browser, IP address, cookie information, and the pages you visit on the site.
In addition to the information that is recorded automatically, we also collect information that you provide to us when you complete an online form or send us e-mail. Bay State College makes no representations concerning the reliability of information collected by, displayed on, or transmitted from this website. Furthermore, while we take reasonable precautions to secure the information we gather through the site, any sharing of personal information over the internet involves some security risk. Bay State College does not warrant that the information transmitted through or displayed on the site will not be accessed by unauthorized individuals, or that it will be delivered free of viruses or other potentially harmful material. To the fullest extent permitted by law, Bay State College specifically disclaims any warranties in connection with the use of this website including, but not limited to, warranties of merchantability, non-infringement or fitness for a particular purpose.
We do not knowingly collect data from individuals under 13 years of age through this site. If you are under the age of 13, you are not authorized to use this site and should immediately stop doing so.
How We May Use or Disclose Personal Information We may share information about you with employees of Bay State College and affiliated entities involved in activities to which it is relevant; with our attorneys, accountants and other professionals; and with third parties who work with us in developing and maintaining the site. We may also use that information for internal testing or training purposes, to help us develop our website to better meet visitors' needs and expectations, or to communicate with you for any purpose. Some information may be stored subject to retention requirements.
Furthermore, Bay State reserves the right to disclose personal information to law enforcement officials, investigators, or other third parties as we deem necessary to prevent or address abuses of the site including, but not limited to, violations of this Internet Privacy Policy, or when such disclosure is required by law.
Occasionally, we may use certain information that we have collected to send you information about programs, products or services offered by Bay State College or other organizations that we think may be of interest to you. However, Bay State College does not sell or rent any personal data submitted by visitors to any unrelated third parties.
Bay State College respects the privacy of users visiting our site and will abide by all applicable laws concerning the release of personal information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. Please e-mail admissions@baystate.edu to request that your name be removed from our mailing lists.
Links to Other Sites This site may contain links to other sites operated by non-affiliated third parties. If you choose to access such third-party sites, the operators of such sites may acquire access to your personal information. You should be aware that Bay State College does not control the information privacy and security policies or practices of such unaffiliated third parties. Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for either the content of such third-party sites or their use (or abuse) of any information they receive from or about you.
Changes to This Policy Bay State College may modify this Internet Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice. If we choose to do so, then the effective date of the change will be identified above the title of this document as the “Last Modified” date. You will be deemed to have agreed to any such modifications by your continued use of this site on or after the “Last Modified” date. We encourage you to review this policy as often as necessary to remain aware of its current contents.
Promotional Messages from Third Party SitesOccasionally, we may display promotional messages on behalf of Bay State College via third party websites. If you would like to opt-out from seeing promotional messages of any kind, please email admissions@baystate.edu to request that your email address be removed from all marketing lists.
Questions Any questions concerning this Internet Privacy Policy may be addressed to admissions@baystate.edu.
What are the computer requirements for participation in an online program?
